let savollar22 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "to accommodate",
      answer: "C. joy bilan ta'minlamoq",
      options: [
        "A. yo'qotmoq",
        "B. yopmoq",
        "C. joy bilan ta'minlamoq",
        "D. otmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "circus",
      answer: "A. sirk",
      options: [
        "A. sirk",
        "B. zavod",
        "C. bekat",
        "D. aeroport"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "to coincide",
      answer: "D. bir vaqtda sodir bo'lmoq",
      options: [
        "A. ajratmoq",
        "B. kurashmoq",
        "C. uchmoq",
        "D. bir vaqtda sodir bo'lmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "to commission",
      answer: "B. buyurtma bermoq",
      options: [
        "A. o'ynamoq",
        "B. buyurtma bermoq",
        "C. suzmoq",
        "D. sayr qilmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "dose",
      answer: "C. doza",
      options: [
        "A. quti",
        "B. tarelka",
        "C. doza",
        "D. savat"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "to dye",
      answer: "A. bo'yamoq",
      options: [
        "A. bo'yamoq",
        "B. pishirmoq",
        "C. tozalamoq",
        "D. tikmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "extent",
      answer: "D. daraja",
      options: [
        "A. narx",
        "B. vaqt",
        "C. joy",
        "D. daraja"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "gender",
      answer: "B. jins",
      options: [
        "A. yosh",
        "B. jins",
        "C. bo'y",
        "D. vazn"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "headline",
      answer: "C. sarlavha",
      options: [
        "A. bob",
        "B. eslatma",
        "C. sarlavha",
        "D. she'r"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "informal",
      answer: "A. norasmiy",
      options: [
        "A. norasmiy",
        "B. murakkab",
        "C. xavfli",
        "D. aniq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "to inquire",
      answer: "D. so'ramoq",
      options: [
        "A. kulmoq",
        "B. yig'lamoq",
        "C. uxlamoq",
        "D. so'ramoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "messenger",
      answer: "B. xabarchi",
      options: [
        "A. oshpaz",
        "B. xabarchi",
        "C. rassom",
        "D. haydovchi"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "to peer",
      answer: "C. tikilmoq",
      options: [
        "A. raqsga tushmoq",
        "B. kuylamoq",
        "C. tikilmoq",
        "D. yugurmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "portrait",
      answer: "A. portret",
      options: [
        "A. portret",
        "B. gilam",
        "C. deraza",
        "D. shkaf"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "to pose",
      answer: "D. qimirlamay turmoq",
      options: [
        "A. yuvmoq",
        "B. tozalamoq",
        "C. dazmollamoq",
        "D. qimirlamay turmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "ranch",
      answer: "B. ferma",
      options: [
        "A. mehmonxona",
        "B. ferma",
        "C. muzey",
        "D. kinoteatr"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "to steer",
      answer: "C. boshqarmoq",
      options: [
        "A. bosmoq",
        "B. chizmoq",
        "C. boshqarmoq",
        "D. buklamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "stripe",
      answer: "A. yo'l-yo'l chiziq",
      options: [
        "A. yo'l-yo'l chiziq",
        "B. nuqta",
        "C. aylana",
        "D. kub"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "tame",
      answer: "D. qo'lga o'rgangan",
      options: [
        "A. ho'l",
        "B. sovuq",
        "C. qattiq",
        "D. qo'lga o'rgangan"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "to tempt",
      answer: "B. qiziqtirmoq",
      options: [
        "A. tejamoq",
        "B. qiziqtirmoq",
        "C. yig'moq",
        "D. tartiblamoq"
      ]
    }
];

export default savollar22;